Zhijiang Capacity Infinite Technology (Zhejiang) Co., Ltd. Zhejiang Yanhe Culture Technology Co., Ltd.
A giant rat demon!
A rat demon!
It's trying to kill me!
A giant rat demon! The rat demon is here!
My lord!
What on earth is going on?
My lord, save me!
A rat demon.
A giant rat demon.
It wants to eat me.
The rat demon.
Don't panic. Get up and tell me slowly.
Last night.
Help!
If I hadn't run fast last night,
I would have been killed by the rat demon.
Feng Er.
You are a famous gambler in Fangzhou.
You always lose money in gambling.
And now you are targeted by a rat demon.
Tell me the truth,
why are you so unlucky?
I don't know either.
I have never offended anyone in my life.
I just love to gamble.
I don't know what happened,
but I provoked this monster.
Please, you must save me.
I don't want to die.
Don't worry. We will definitely catch the rat demon.
You said
you saw the rat demon right here.
Yes, right here.
How about I pack up and hide somewhere for a few days?
No.
Don't go anywhere tonight.
We will protect you.
We wake up earlier than roosters
and sleep later than dogs.
Who can stand working like this every day?
I think that monster must be...
Who is it?
Mr. Shen.
What did you bring?
What are you doing here so late?
Of course I'm bringing someone some late-night snacks and wine.
I'm not hungry.
The files from the Ministry of Revenue in Chang'an,
do you want to take a look?
There was a wealthy family in Chang'an
named Xu.
They came to Fangzhou to worship their ancestors,
but their four-year-old son went missing.
They searched everywhere but couldn't find him.
Later, their family declined,
and the couple passed away one after another.
Now,
they have no descendants.
Then what does the son of the Xu family
have to do with the rat demon?
This jade pendant is proof of identity.
Either
the rat demon stole it,
or
it originally belonged to him.
The rat demon
probably won't show up tonight.
How about we start eating?
Let's eat.
Come on.
Wait a minute.
What food did you bring?
Just some chicken legs
and a jar of wine.
Oh my god.
It startled me.
I almost broke this jar of fine wine.
What is that?
Beat it!
Stop.
After him.
You.
Where are you?
You wanna fight me,
you little brat.
The way I beat you back then,
is how I will beat you today.
Little mouse.
Don't let me catch you.
If I do, I will tear you to pieces.
Anything?
Nothing.
Hurry, search outside.
A whole group of you were standing guard,
yet you still let that monster
slip away right under your noses.
And Zhang Chao here even got injured.
How do you all do your jobs?
My lord.
It was my incompetence.
I failed to catch the monster.
My lord.
I am responsible for this.
Alright.
I bought the chicken legs and wine,
which gave the monster a chance.
I see.
But you were only trying to reward the boys.
Magistrate, please give us one more chance.
Two days.
I will definitely solve the case within two days.
How about
two more days?
Right.
Two more days.
No need.
Lord Su.
What are you doing here?
There could be anything in Yeren Valley.
When someone blows the whistle,
I'll have to protect her.
I don't need your protection.
This someone
bragged
about solving the case in two days.
I'd better accompany you.
Fine.
Come along then.